Bye-bye. I just got us reservations at Michelle's and tickets to the music band to celebrate
our first holiday season as a betrothed couple.
Betrothed.
Betrothed couple.
Hey.
Huh?
Oh.
Pheebs?
Huh?
Skull?
Oh, yeah, it's my mom's.
Oh, my God!
No, no, no, it's not, it's not my mom.
It belonged to my mom.
Yeah, no, she used to put it out every Christmas to remind us that even though it's Christmas,
people still die.
And you can put candy in it.
Hey.
Hey, I just found out I get Ben for the holidays this year.
Oh, that's great.
Are you gonna dress up as Santa?
Nope.
I mean, I know Susan does every year,
but I think I want to take this year to teach him all about Hanukkah.
And maybe I could teach Ben about the Christmas skull and how people die.
You may need to use this year to teach Ben about Phoebe.
Mm.
Hey.
Did you know I was in there?
No.
How long have we been home?
About a half an hour.
Lovely.
Hey, you know what I was thinking?
When we get married, are you gonna, uh,
change your last name to Bing?
Nope.
Why not?
Bing's weird.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Dillard.
Oh, hey, you guys.
Hey.
Guess what?
My landlord just called, and my apartment's gonna be ready soon,
so I guess I'll be moving out.
Aw, Phoebe, I'm gonna miss you.
Yes, you will be very sad.
All right, well, I gotta go tell Rachel the good news.
Oh, are you guys gonna be living together again?
Yeah, why not?
Well, she's just having so much fun with Joey,
I just assumed she'd still be living with him.
Why do you think she's having so much fun living with Joey?
No reason, except she...
told me.
Really? So she said she didn't want to live with me anymore?
No, no, she didn't say that.
I think you should talk to Monica now.
Phoebe, don't worry about it.
I'm sure she wants to live with you.
You're sure? You're absolutely sure?
Well, no, but she probably does.
Probably?
Yeah, I don't like that word.
I know what probably really means.
Yeah, mm-hmm, yeah.
Oh, your mom probably won't kill herself.
You know, no, you know.
No, the funeral director probably won't hit on you.
Yeah, that nice couple probably will adopt you.
Yeah, okay, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but I'm not hanging all my hopes
of Rachel and I living together on probably.
You know, you've got to take care of yourself.
This world, you know, history teaches us nothing.
Bing doesn't seem so weird now, does it?
Hey, great, you're home.
Guess what Phoebe got me for Christmas.
Drums?
No, drums!
Hi, can we get two burritos to go, please?
I'm sorry, but not that sorry,
because you don't have to live with it.
We have a reservation under the name Chandler Bing.
Okay, we'll have a table for you in about 45 minutes.
45 minutes?
We have tickets to the Music Man at 8.
I'm sorry, Christmas is a very busy time, sir.
Is this because of the burrito thing?
You need to give him money.
Give him money? It was a joke.
No, to get a table.
Places like this are always shaking you down.
Everybody wants a payoff.
All right, calm down, O'Malley.
I'll slip him some money.
You've got to be smooth about it.
Hey, I can be smooth.
Listen, we're in a little bit of a hurry,
so if you could get us a table a little quicker,
I'd appreciate it.
Of course, sir.
Okay.
How'd it go?
Had the money in the wrong hand.
Hey, you don't feel like you're going to throw up, do you?
No.
Well, I do, so let's...
So, Ben, you, uh...
You know what holiday is coming up, don't you?
Christmas.
Yep, and you know what other holiday is coming up?
Christmas Eve.
Yes, but also...
Hanukkah?
See, you're part Jewish, and Hanukkah is a Jewish holiday.
Santa has rangers that can fly.
Right, but on Hanukkah,
Hanukkah is the celebration of a miracle.
See, years and years ago,
there were these people called the Maccabees.
Jingle bells, jingle bells.
Okay, yes, that's right, yes,
but on Hanukkah, we sing,
♪ Dreidel, dreidel, dreidel, I made you out of clay ♪
♪ Rudolph the red-nosed reindeer... ♪
Okay, it's not a contest.
When is Santa coming?
Well, how about this year,
instead of Santa,
we have fun celebrating Hanukkah?
No Santa?
Was I bad?
No, oh, no, no, no, hey,
you weren't bad, you've been very good, Ben.
Santa's mad at me.
No, hey, hey, come on.
Ben, Santa is not mad at you, okay?
You're his favorite little guy.
So Santa's coming?
Yes!
Santa's coming!
Will he bring me an ant farm?
Will you keep it at Mommy's?
Okay.
Then sure.
Look, maybe this slipping him money thing
is not gonna work, you know?
Maybe we should just wait.
You're the one who said you would die
if you didn't see Music Man.
I didn't say die.
I said cry.
It's easy, just keep it casual.
Give him a kind word, shake his hand,
and give him the money.
How do you know so much about this?
I don't know.
Richard used to do it, didn't he?
He'd be eating our soup right now.
Mustache bastard.
Okay, those people just left.
Come on, quick, give them the money.
We'll get their table.
Excuse me.
Ah, ha, ha, ha.
So you like the drums?
Oh, that's, that's great.
You know, I was worried that, you know,
they would create maybe an unbearable
living situation, but...
Okay, well, apparently not, so yay!
Hey, hey, Deeps, check it out.
We already learned a song.
Ready?
One, two, three, four.
Tequila!
That's fun.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You got there? Put it there.
Definitely not easier with coins.
Thank you.
Hey, hey, hey.
Here, now I only owe you 49.50.
Hey, Pheebs.
Hey.
If you want to get Joey a Christmas present
that disrupts the entire building,
why not get him something a little bit more subtle,
like a wrecking ball or a vial of smallpox
to release in the hallway?
It's not just the drum noise.
Every five minutes,
Joey throws his sticks in the air,
and I have to hear,
Oh, my eye! Oh, God, my eye!
I mean, it's so annoying.
Yes, thank you.
You see, this is how normal people
are supposed to react to drums.
Phoebe, you got Joey drums to annoy Rachel
so she wouldn't want to live there anymore?
Maybe on some level.
Joey, you know that you could just not
throw the sticks up in the air.
What is rock and roll about that?
Hey, Joey.
I got you another present.
Okay, what is it?
Uh, it's a tarantula!
Oh!
God!
Rachel, I'm sorry.
What was I thinking,
giving Joey this big, gross, scary spider
in such a poorly constructed cage?
What are you talking about?
I love them!
I had a tarantula when I was a kid.
But it died because my cat ate it.
And then, yeah, my cat died.
But, Joey, isn't this cool?
Is it on me?
I feel like it's on me.
Oh, isn't that adorable?
Joey is afraid of the tarantula.
Oh, yeah.
He's so adorable.
God, he's just so much fun.
Joey's the best.
I'm glad you're having so much fun here.
Whoa, wait, wait.
What, Phoebe, what's the matter?
Our apartment is ready.
And that makes you angry because...
Because you would rather live here with Joey.
Where did you get that?
Monica and Chandler said that you were having so much fun here.
And apparently no amount of drums or tarantulas is gonna change that.
Phoebe?
Hmm?
Did you get all this stuff for Joey
to try and drive me out of the apartment?
Honey, if you wanted to do that,
you might as well have just gotten him a fish.
You know how fish freak me out?
Fish.
But it wouldn't have mattered anyway, Phoebe.
You and I are gonna live together.
We're roommates. That's the deal.
Yes, but I wanted you to want to live with me.
But, okay, if you're having so much fun over here...
Oh, it's so much more fun with you.
We did have fun, didn't we?
We had so much fun.
You remember that time we were playing with the Super Bowl
and we accidentally threw it through the window and it broke?
I remember paying for the window,
but I don't remember how it broke.
Yeah, stuff like that.
Yeah, yeah.
Anyway, they say if we want, we could see it tonight.
Ah, I would love to!
Yay, okay!
Great! All right, good!
Oh, and Monica asked me to make the drumming stop.
Um...
Done!
Hey.
Hello, sir. You here to return those pants?
No, these are my pants.
Oh. Okay.
How can I help you?
Well, um, do you have a Santa outfit left?
Two days before Christmas?
Sorry, man. Did you try Costume City?
Yeah, yeah, I've tried everywhere.
Please, please, I mean, I'll pay extra.
Sorry, but I do have 74 of them coming back on the 26th.
Okay, look, do you have anything Christmassy?
I promised my son and I really don't want to disappoint him.
Um, come on, you gotta have something.
I'm the Holiday Armadillo!
I'm a friend of Santa's,
and he sent me here to wish you a Merry Christmas!
What happened to Santa, Holiday Armadillo?
Santa was unavailable so close to Christmas.
Oh, come in, have a seat.
You must be exhausted coming all the way from Texas.
Texas?
That's right, Ben.
I'm Santa's representative for all the southern states.
And Mexico!
But Santa sent me here to give you these presents, Ben.
Maybe the lady will help me with these presents.
Wow!
Wow, thanks!
You're welcome, Ben. Merry Christmas.
And Happy Hanukkah!
Are you for Hanukkah too? Because I'm part Jewish.
You are? Me too!
Because armadillos also wandered in the desert?
You want to wander in the hall?
Hey, Ben!
What if the Holiday Armadillo told you all about the Festival of Lights?
Cool!
Come on, Ben.
Years and years ago, there were these people called the Maccabees.
Ho, ho, ho! Merry Christmas!
Santa!
Hey!
What are you doing here, Santa?
Well, I'm here to see my old buddy, Ben.
What are you doing here?
Weird... turtle men?
I'm the Holiday Armadillo!
Your part Jewish friend!
You sent me here to give Ben some presents, remember?
What?
Did you bring me any presents, Santa?
You bet I did, Ben! Put it there!
Well, it would have worked this time if his hands weren't so damn small.
Ho, ho, ho!
Okay, Ben, why don't you come open some more presents,
and Santa, the Armadillo, and I will have a little talk in the kitchen.
There's a sentence I never thought I'd say.
What are you doing?
You called everyone and said you were having trouble finding a Santa costume,
so I borrowed one from a guy at work.
Thank you, but you gotta leave.
Why?
Because I'm finally getting him excited about Hanukkah!
I mean, you're wrecking it!
But I didn't get to shake my belly like a bowl full of jelly!
I'm sorry, Chandler, but this is really important to me.
Okay, fine, I'll give the suit back.
Hey, you think you can keep it another night?
Santa? Really?
Yeah, is that okay?
Did your dad ever dress up like Santa?
No.
Then it's okay!
Okay, Ben, Santa has to go. Say goodbye!
No, why does he have to go?
Because if Santa and the holiday...
Armadillo...
are ever in the same room for too long, the universe will implode!
Merry Christmas!
No, why can't the Armadillo leave? I want Santa!
Fine, I give up. Santa can stay!
Well, I'll stay, but only because I want to hear about Hanukkah.
Ben, will you sit here with Santa and learn about Hanukkah?
Okay, Santa!
All right, it's time for the story of Hanukkah!
Years and years ago, there were these people called the Maccabees!
Merry Christmas!
Oh, wow! Look at this place!
Oh, this is terrible!
Oh, they've made so many changes, I can't even feel my grandmother's presence anymore!
Oh, new sconces!
Oh, my God!
What?
Okay, remember how you told me that your grandmother put up that wall to make that into two bedrooms?
Yeah.
And remember how you always said you were afraid that the landlord would find out and then tear it down?
Do you really not know where I'm going with this?
No, of course I do!
Okay.
What?
It left! It's one huge room!
Oh, no!
Wow!
See?
Well, I guess we'll just have to put the wall back up.
You can't, because of the new skylight!
There's a skylight?
Wow!
So, what should we do? Should we start looking for a new place?
You know, I'm sensing that my grandmother would not be comfortable with that.
Oh, yeah? Starting to feel her again there, are we?
A little bit, yeah.
Phoebes, is your grandmother maybe saying that you should live here alone?
You heard it, too! You have the gift!
Phoebe, it's okay! I like living with Joey!
Are you sure?
Oh, please! I hate packing! It's closer to work, and we do have fun!
Although, I'm really going to miss living with you.
Oh, me too.
Oh, oh, wait! Did you hear that? Hear that? Listen!
Huh?
I'm getting something from your grandmother.
She said that since you get to keep the one-bedroom apartment, you should give Rachel the purple chair?
I do not hear that.
Oh, no, wait a minute. Oh, okay. She didn't say chair, she said share.
You should share the one-bedroom apartment.
Oh, the purple chair! No, yeah, I heard that.
And the miracle was that that little bit of oil that should have lasted just one day burned for...
Eight whole days.
That's right, and that's why we celebrate Hanukkah today. The end.
Awesome!
My favorite part was when Superman flew all the Jews out of Egypt.
The armadillo was actually not so thrilled about that part.
Why is Santa kissing Aunt Monica?
Because Aunt Monica was very, very good this year.
Okay, Ben, it's time to light the Hanukkah candles!
Hey! Oh, wow! Looks like the Easter Bunny's funeral in here.
Come on, come on. We're lighting the candles. Come on.
I understand why Superman is here, but why is there a porcupine at the Easter Bunny's funeral?
Did you get it?
I got it.
Is it back in the cage?
It's back in the cage.
The cage closed.
Joey, will you just come out here and stop being such a baby?